<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UVCE Connect</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">125839481353081</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb125839481353081</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Year">Year :</string>
    <string name="department">Department :</string>
    <string name="continue_to_be_removed_at_release">Continue(TO be removed at release)</string>
    <string name="PREF_FILE">APP_PRIF_FILE</string>
    <string name="LOGIN_TYPE">APP_LOGIN_TYPE</string>

    <string name="title_activity_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_activity_campus__says">Campus Says</string>

    <!--HACK! DONT CHANGE THE NAME, Feel free to change the value!-->
    <string name="arch">Architecture</string>
    <string name="cse">Computer Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="ce">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="eee">Electronic and Electrical Engineering</string>
    <string name="ece">Electronics and Communication Engineering</string>
    <string name="ise">Information Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="me">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>

    <string-array name="branch_array">
        <item>@string/arch</item>
        <item>@string/cse</item>
        <item>@string/ce</item>
        <item>@string/ece</item>
        <item>@string/eee</item>
        <item>@string/ise</item>
        <item>@string/me</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="semester_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="year_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="disclaimer">
        UVCE Connect has made honest effort to gather document from various departments.
        The validation of such documents may vary along with time.
        We appreciate users to contribute towards the same.
    </string>

    <string name="Note">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            <b> Note: </b>
            Downloaded file contains syllabus for both
            even and odd semester.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_navigation_main">navigation_main</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_asscociations">asscociations</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_associations">associations</string>
    <string name="title_activity_g2c2">g2c2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_news__adding">Add News</string>
    <string name="title_activity_campus__adding">Add Campus_Says</string>
    <string name="about_coll">UVCE was established in the year 1917, under the name, Government Engineering college by BharatRatna Sir M Visvesvaraya, and was affiliated to University of Mysore.It is the 5th Engineering College to be established in the country.after the formation of Bangalore University in 1964, UVCE became one of the constituent college of Bangalore University. This is one of the oldest technical institutions in the country, imparting technical education leading to B.E, M.E, B.Arch, M.Sc (Engineering) and Ph D degrees in the various disciplines of Engineering and Architecture. It has completed 93 years of academic excellence since its inception. This pioneer has grown many folds and has acquired a leading position in technical education and is rated among the top 15 Engineering colleges in the country situate at K R Circle and in the neighbourhood of Vidhana Soudha, Govt of Karnataka, the city campus is housing the Department of Mechanical Engineering, Department of Electrical Engineering. Department of Electronics Engineering and Department of Computer Science and Engineering. Proximity to city bus stand connects one easily to any part of the city. Amidst the Jnana Bharathi campus, the hub of Bangalore University, Post graduate Academic activities, the Engineering campus has departments of Civil Engineering and Architecture.  UVCE is recognized by the All India Council of Technical Education (AICTE) of the Govt of India and is a recipient of financial aid under World Bank’s Technical Education Quality Improvement Programme(TEQIP). UVCE has a NAAC rating of 5 Star for the past 4 consecutive years issued by the National Board of Accreditation. UVCE does not limit itself to being technically extravagant but also it is culturally diversified. The campus will be buzzing with activities all through the year, which provides opportunities to students to showcase their talent and prove their mettle in various genres. In a way, UVCE not only shapes the careers of its students but also makes them fit to face the real world challenges that are posed in the society. UVCE is witnessing even more positive improvements and is here to stay for very long time. The best part in UVCE has been the teacher-student partnership in achieving the missions and goals set. The students engross themselves enthusiastically and actively in the research work and gain knowledge before they venture either into the professional world or the teaching spectra. This facilitates the al round growth of any student here in the UVCE campus. Dr. Venugopal K. R. has been in Bangalore University for the last four decades. He has Eleven Degrees with Ph.D. in Computer Science Engineering from IIT-Madras, Chennai and another Ph.D. in Economics from Bangalore University. He has degrees in Law, Mass Communication, Electronics, Economics, Business Finance, Computer Science, Public Relations and Industrial Relations. He has authored and edited 64 books and published more than 600 papers in refereed International Journals and International Conferences. He has supervised 630 M.E. dissertations, 22 Ph.Ds and filed 101 Patents. He was a Post Doctoral Research Scholar and a visiting Professor at University of Southern California, USA. He has been conferred Fellow of IEEE, USA and ACM Distinguished Educator for contributions to Computer Science Engineering and Electrical Engineering Education.
    \t \t \t\t\t\t\t\t \t\t\t\t\tDr. Venugopal K R\n
B.E., M.A., D.J., L.L.B., B.S., D.P.R., M.B.F., D.I.R., M.E.,\n
Ph.D. (Computer Science), Ph.D. (Economics), FIEEE (USA)\n
ACM Distinguished Educator (USA)\n
Principal, University Visvesvaraya College of Engineering, Bangalore University, Bangalore\n
Special Officer, Government of Karnataka (December 2012 – June 2016)\n
\t \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t\t\t\tFormer:\n
Dean, Faculty of Engineering, Member of Syndicate and Academic Council,\n
Professor, Department of Computer Science and Engineering,\n
University Visvesvaraya College of Engineering\nBangalore University, Bangalore – 560001.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ieee">ieee</string>
    <string name="title_activity_academic">Academic</string>
    <string name="about_uvce">
        UVCE then called ‘College of Engineering’ was established at Bengaluru in 1917 just a year after the University of Mysore was established, giving a fillip to higher education and to enable the students of Mysore State to play their part in the Engineering field. \n\n

Initially, two branches of engineering namely, Civil and Mechanical Engineering were started. College of Engineering (UVCE) was the 5th Engineering College of the country and first in the Princely State of Mysore. \n\n

UVCE currently offers \n
1.	Seven Undergraduate (B.E / B.Arch) \n
2.	Twenty-Four Postgraduate (M.E / M.Arch.) \n
3.	Three Part time BE evening under graduate courses. \n
4.	M.Sc. (Engineering) by Research, \n
5.	Three-Year full time Ph.D., \n
6.	Four-Year part time Ph.D. programmes in all disciplines. \n
7.	Ph.D. (QIP) programme in Civil Engineering\n \n

The total intake of the college is about 1200 students a year.

    </string>
    <string name="about_po">
    Training and Placement Office is the power house of UVCE where, Student coordinators take the responsibility to interact with companies under the guidance of Placement Officer Dr. Thriveni. Placement Office was established in the year 1989, and has been consistently working as a liaison between the industry and students in order to fulfil the ambition of the students in getting the right job. \n\n
    About 90% of our students are placed in globally recognized companies with attractive offers. Batch of 2016 witnessed an all-time record of grabbing around 1060 offers.\n \n

    Email: info@campusuvce.in/  \n
    Contact:  +91 789903 7717 / 080-22276070 \n
    Website: http://campusuvce.in/ \n
    </string>
    <string name="about_g2c2">
        To accomplish the purpose of Clean and Green UVCE, a student led initiative, "Go Green and Clean Club" which is simply known as G2C2 was started in the year 2014 by a group of ME CSE department students. It is now run by enthusiasts from 2nd and 3rd year BE students. Presently it has about 100 voluntary members who are dedicated towards the cause. \n \n
Club aims to involve college faculty, alumni and larger number of students in future days to improve its effectiveness. \n \n

Email: gogreenuvce@gmail.com \n\n
Contact: Harsha S (9480281997) \n \n

    </string>

    <string name="about_vinimaya">
        Books are a collection of enormous amount of knowledge and guidance in a compressed form; it is a vital asset for the mankind. ‘VINIMAYA’ meaning ‘Sharing’ in Kannada, works on this very basic principle. Books that a student has can be shared with the club and the books that VINIMAYA has can be borrowed by the students. There\'s no worry if one doesn\'t have a book to share. \n \n
Wait it\’s not just books…! VINIMAYA also shares TV series, Anime, Movies, Ted Talks, E-Books for the one who seeks. Any student can drop into G2C2 room and borrow their favourite book, anime, movie, without any membership.  \n \n

Website: - http://aliengo.000webhostapp.com/first/vini2.0/vini2home.php \n \n
Contact: - Thanush (8867768009) \n


    </string>

    <string name="about_thathva">

        We are aware of the fact that RAMESH ARAVIND, DATTANNA, MANOHMURTHY are namma UVCE’s proud alumni who with their skills have created an everlasting impact on Kannada film industry.\n \n
UVCE’s leading collegiate Club which aims to improve one\'s skill in acting is Thathva. \n \n
Thathva was established by Abhishek Chakma from ECE batch of 2015. Currently Thathva consists of 60+ students involved in the activity. Members of Thathva took part in a street play ensemble called Manthan which took place in Forum mall, Kormangala. \n \n
The main objective is to \n \n
* Promote theatre in college \n
* Set up a platform for theatre enthusiasts\n
* To collaborate and do what they love \n\n
Contact: Darshan (8867362582)


    </string>

    <string name="about_sae">
        Society of automotive Engineers (SAE) is a World-Wide organization which sets standards and validates automotive projects. A student branch of this organization exists in UVCE. The motto of SAE-INDIA stands as ‘The Engineering Society for Advancing Mobility in Land Sea Air and Space’. \n\n
GKDC (go-cart building championship), BAJA (Pronounced as BAHA, is an all-terrain vehicle building championship), SUPRA (Racing car building championship) are the main National Level competition organised by SAE. \n\n
The student branch of SAE, ‘SAE-INDIA UVCE’ was set up in 2011 due to the earnest efforts of Mechanical Students of Batch 2009-2013. The club till date has involved in conducting many activities to benefit the members for improving their skills in the technical field. \n\n
Team Em-power UVCE stood 6th (AIR) in GKDC and 124th(AIR) In BAJA are some of the acclaimed achievements of the group till date. \n\n

Email: sae.uvce@gmail.com \n\n
Contact: Adithya Pai (9446325235)

    </string>

    <string name="about_vision_UVCE">
       VisionUVCE is a group of UVCE alumni who are focussed on \"Giving Back to UVCE\" by creating awareness among the strong alumni and make them understand the potential that the creation of an alumni group, working for the betterment of college brings about.\n\n
It is VU\'s responsibility to make sure, the flag of our alma mater flies high in the air and also as proud alumni of this college, there is a need to take part in the operations involved with the institution.\n\n
Major programs held under VISION UVCE:\n\n
1	Sampada – A monthly magazine that offers you a ride though UVCE\n
2	VU scholarship – Every year scholarships are provided to those in need\n
3	VU champs – Recognition of efforts of Student Volunteers\n
4	Parichaya – A detailed profile of UVCE’s great alumni\n
5	Samvaada – Occasional meet between alumnus, current staff and students\n
6	VU also supports and funds various student initiatives which seems promising in terms of idea and its reach. It\'s also involved in taking care of student\’s utility in campus by funding to the required cause. VU raises its fund from alumni of UVCE.\n\n

Website:  http://www.visionuvce.in \n\n
Email: contact@visionuvce.in\n\n
Contact:  +91-9740111552
    </string>

    <string name="about_UVCE_Foundations">
        The UVCE Foundation was created by alumni, faculty and well-wishers of UVCE in 2003 to help in restoring the glory of UVCE. It has members from around the world and has already executed various projects at UVCE to address immediate needs of the students of UVCE \n\n
UVCE Foundation has been growing in strength ever since its inception and has been widely recognized as a strong support from the college authorities. The objective of the Foundation is to restore the ‘top-ten’ status the college.\n\n

Website: http://uvcefoundation.org

    </string>

    <string name="about_chethana">
        ನಾವು ಕನ್ನಡಿಗರು, ವಿಶಾಲ ಹೃದಯವನ್ನು ಹೊಂದವರು, ಜಗತ್ತಿನ ಮೂಲೆ-ಮೂಲೆಗಳಿಂದ ಹರಿದುಬರುವ ಜನರನ್ನು ತನ್ನ ಓಡಿಲಲ್ಲಿ ಸಾಕಿ ಸಲಹುವವರು. ಈ ಸಲಹುವಿಕೆ ಹೆಚ್ಚಾಯಿತೇನೋ, ಬೆಂಗಳೂರಿನಲ್ಲಿ ಕನ್ನಡಿಗರೇ ಅಲ್ಪಸಂಖ್ಯಾತರಾಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ. ಕನ್ನಡತನ ಎಂಬುದು ಮುಗಿದುಹೋದ ಅಧ್ಯಾಯವಾಗತೊಡಗಿದೆ. ಇಡೀಯ ಜಗತ್ತಿನಲ್ಲಿ ಅಂಗೈಯಷ್ಟು ಅಗಲ ಜಾಗದಲ್ಲಿ ಮಾತ್ರ ಕನ್ನಡ ಉಸಿರಾಡುತ್ತಿದೆ. ಕನ್ನಡವನ್ನು ಬಳಸುವ, ಉಳಿಸುವ, ಬೆಳೆಸುವ ಕೆಲಸ ಮಾಡಬೇಕಿದೆ. \n\n
ನಮ್ಮೆಲ್ಲರಲ್ಲೂ ಕನ್ನಡಾಭಿಮಾನ ಭೂದಿ ಮುಚ್ಚಿದ ಕೆಂಡದಂತಿದೆ. ಹಾಗೆಯೇ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಂಸ್ಥೆಯಲ್ಲಿ ಕನ್ನಡಾಭಿಮಾನಿಗಳು ಹರಿದು ಹಂಚಿಹೋಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ, ಹಾಗೂ ಕನ್ನಡವೇ ಉಸಿರು ಎಂದು ಬದುಕುತ್ತಿರುವವರು ಎಲೆಮರೆಯ ಕಾಯಿಯಂತಾಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ. ಇವರನ್ನೆಲ್ಲಾ ಒಂದುಗೂಡಿಸುವ ಪ್ರಯತ್ನ ಚೇತನದ ಉದ್ದೇಶ. \n\n
ಕನ್ನಡದ ಏಳಿಗೆಗಾಗಿ, ಅದರ ಸಾರ್ವಬೌಮತೆಗಾಗಿ , ಕನ್ನಡಾಂಬೆ  ಸೇವೆಗಾಗಿ ಹುಟ್ಟಿಕೊಂಡ ಗುಂಪು ಚೇತನ. ಇಲ್ಲಿ ಸಾಹಿತ್ಯ ಉತ್ಖನನ, ಸಂಗೀತ ಸಮರ್ಪಣಾ ಹಾಗೂ ವಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಏಳಿಗೆಗೆ ಶ್ರಮಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ. \n\n
ಸಂಪರ್ಕಿಸಿ: - ವೆಂಕಟೇಶ್ ಬೆಳವಾಡಿ (9482909698) \n\n
ಮಿಂಚಂಚೆ:-  uvcekannadasanga.chetana@gmail.com

    </string>

    <string name="about_alumni_association">
        Alumni are the vital asset for any educational institution. UVCE being a century old college finds its alumni spread widely across globe. Alumni association aims to gather its strong alumni network and build a better UVCE with its various initiatives like, \n\n
1.	Lecture series \n
2.	Providing scholarship \n
3.	Corpus funds \n
4.	Awarding achievers \n
5.	Planning Centenary building \n
6.	Community service \n \n

The alumni association strives to keep its members informed about the activities that happen in the college through its newsletter. \n\n
Website: http://uvcealumni.org/index.html

    </string>

    <string name="about_fests">
        CULTURAL\n\n
UVCE JAATHRE: As the name indicates, it\'s a colourful one day event organised by 2nd year students during the month of Oct every year. During this event various collegiate clubs\’ setup their stall at quadrangle of main campus and conduct fun games, thereby helping freshers to know about UVCE. \n\n
FIESTA: It\'s a one day intra collegiate Cultural fest of UVCE organised by 3rd year students in odd semester. It\'s a Cultural extravaganza which accelerates UVCEians to participate in widespread events. Students from every department of UVCE participate in this fest.\n\n
CIVISTA: This event is similar to fiesta but this being celebrated by Civil Students at Jnana Bharathi campus. Civista is the annual Cultural fest of Civil department and is organised by 3rd year students. It attracts huge number of participants from the Bangalore University campus.\n\n
ESPORTIVO: Sports has a high calibre in UVCE. The craze setup for football and cricket is everlasting in the century old college. Esportivo is a week-long event organised by sports geeks to uphold the sportsmanship sprit among various teams across Bengaluru.\n\n
MILAGRO: MILAGRO is the biggest cultural festival in UVCE organised by final year students which spans over two days. However, the entire week will be called as Milagro Week and various events are held to entertain the students. With the history of two decades, it provides a platform where every individual in college comes together to create a difference. It upholds the pride of UVCE and culture of Karnataka. It has always been dealt with grandeur and festivity. \n\n

TECHNICAL\n\n
KAGADA: It\'s a National level technical symposium, organised by Team IEEE UVCE. Students across the country take part in this event where they get to showcase their technical knowledge and research by means of Paper and Poster presentation. The best paper and posters are awarded. \n\n

INSPIRON:  Inspiron is an inter college technical fest organized by The Training and Placement Office, UVCE. It is an entrepreneurship and management extravaganza which has various events that requires one to showcase technical, entrepreneurship and managerial skills.  It is conducted every year in odd semester.\n\n

IMPETUS: IMPETUS is a National Level Technical Extravaganza organized by IEEE UVCE. IMPETUS is a technical fest designed for a change and with a vivid difference. Unlike other fests, every year this fest goes out with a message for the engineers. The fest was themed after Engineering for Society followed by Innovation and Entrepreneurship in 2013. This 2 day long fest has always had a diverse participation from all over the country. Over the years IMPETUS has emerged to be one of Bengaluru\'s top technical fests.

    </string>

    <string name="about_chakravyua">
        Life is full of surprises, Adventure is a part and parcel of engineering life. In this limited 4years an engineering student would have experienced lot of unforgettable moments. To quench one\'s thirst for Adventure \"Chakravyuha\" the trekking club of UVCE was started by students.\n\n
Club usually holds 2 trekking drives in each semester. Starting point of every trek being UVCE, it tries to explore trekking spots across Bengaluru within a tight budget and give students an adventure experience.\n\n
The recent treks being \n\n
1.	Kunthi betta \n
2.	Makalidurga \n
3.	Tadiyandanmol \n
4.	Chanarayanna durga \n\n
Contact:- Yashvanth (9448430215)

    </string>

    <string name="about_sports">
        Sports at UVCE have remained at its best by the sportsman skill of UVCEians. The physical education department is led by Dr. Lokesh Reddy who is the mentor and monitor of sports at UVCE. \n\n
UVCE have its football team and cricket team which is recognized across the state for its excellence in their respective field. Selection process happens once in a year and teams practice in Bangalore University ground located close to UVCE campus.

    </string>

    <string name="about_NCC">
        Unity and Discipline\’ is the motto of every cadet. In living up to its motto, the NCC strives to be and is one of the greatest cohesive forces of the nation, bringing together the youth hailing from different parts of the country and moulding them into united, secular and disciplined citizens of the nation. \n\n
Details about NCC: -\n\n
Regiment: NO 2 KAR AIR SQUADRON NCC\n\n
AIR WING \n\n
COMMAND: KAR and GOA DIRECTORATE\n\n
BANGALORE B GROUP \n\n
STRENGTH:200\n\n
Practice done on every Saturday 1200 hours to 1700 hours\n\n
Annual intake in the month of July and August.\n\n
Contact:- Balasubramani (886162992)

    </string>

    <string name="about_8GBRam">
        Bangalore based, namma UVCE\’s home band, formed by likeminded music loving people, not only have entertained their crowd and have bagged numerous awards, but also holds the glory of performing in various international conference. The uniqueness of 8GB RAM lies in the skilful modification of music track, they also have added life to melodious composition and proved their passion towards the field of music.  \n\n
Currently 8 GB RAM consists of 8 members, who believes in winning the crowd and not just the trophy. Members of band have similar interests in Indian classical and Carnatic music. Interested to have them in your event….?\n\n
Contact: - Sanjay (9482218283)

    </string>
    <string name="search_name">Search by name</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_by_phone">Search by phone</string>
    <string name="sort_by_key">Sort by key</string>
    <string name="sort_alphabetically">Sort alphabetically</string>
</resources>

